Yu Cong

email: yu.cong.143@gmail.com

Education

B.S., Computer Science, University of Electronic Science and Technology of China, 2020 to 2024 (expc.) B.S., Finance, Southwestern University of Finance and Economics, 2020 to 2024 (expc.)

Weighted Average: 88.85 GPA: 3.91 CET4: 598 CET6: 542

Advanced Algorithms and Program Design Experiments 94 Information Theory and Coding Theory 96 Algorithm for Optimization 95 Financial Econometrics I 94 Financial Econometrics II 96

Honors and Awards

Pacesetter Scholarship, UESTC, 2021

Research Experience

UESTC, Algorithms and Logic Group

2021-2022

Advisors: Toru Takisaka, Bakhadyr Khoussainov

Try to design a faster algorithm for Büchi Games. I did implementations for our new algorithm and some existing algorithms for Büchi Games.

UESTC, Algorithms and Logic Group

2022-2023

Advisors: Chao Xu, Yi Zhou

We studied the incentive allocation problem and designed an algorithm to compute the entire trade-off curve between budget and profit. We submitted a paper to IJCAI 2023.

Projects

Trajectory Query System. I participated in developing an anonymous trajectory similarity query system. The query system includes 3 kinds of server programs and one Android application. We use Proxy Re-Encryption method and homomorphic encryption to protect user trajectories. github repo. This is a project in the ongoing National College Information Security Competition 2023.

Technical Skills

- Programming Language: C++
- Optimization Tool: Gurobi

Personal Statement

I am interested in algorithms and have a little theoretical computer background. During my undergraduate period, I participated in UESTC's competitive programming training and had two research experiences in the Algorithms and Logic group. Majoring in computer science and finance may give me a different view of solving problems.